Turned it on after all these years
오랜만에 전원을 켰어
Dust on the cartridge dust on the screen
카트리지에도 화면에도 먼지가 쌓였네
Three empty slots where stories lived
이야기가 살았던 세 칸은 비어있네
Like someone erased a dream
누군가 꿈을 지운 것처럼
But the cursor blinks on slot one
하지만 커서는 첫 번째 칸에서 깜빡여
And it whispers something new
그리고 새로운 걸 속삭이네
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상
Hundred hours gone without a trace
수백 시간 흔적도 없이 사라졌어
No saved princess no final score
구한 공주도, 최종 점수도 없네
But my hands still know the buttons
하지만 내 손은 여전히 버튼들을 기억해
And the music plays once more
그리고 음악은 다시 한번 흘러나와
So the cursor blinks on slot one
그래서 커서는 첫 번째 칸에서 깜빡여
And I press it knowing now
그리고 이제 알면서 그걸 눌러
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상
Start again from nothing
아무것도 없는 곳에서 다시 시작해
Every blank page holds a song
모든 빈 페이지엔 노래가 담겨 있어
All the maps are waiting
모든 지도가 기다리고 있어
Undrawn worlds where I belong
내가 속할 그려지지 않은 세상